One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Not Here
ليس هنا
Treasure Repository
مستودع الكنوز
What a cute creature you are!
يا لك من مخلوق لطيف
You're a skeleton from tip to toe, and yet somehow you're still alive.
أنت هيكل عظمي من رأسك إلى أخمص قدميك ورغم ذلك ما تزال حيًّا. يا لها من معجزة
You put up a pretty good fight, Soul King.
طريقة قتالك كانت مذهلة أيضًا يا ملك السول
The Chess Peacekeepers are totally afraid of you.
جنود الشطرنج كانوا يرتعدون خوفًا منك
There's a reason you're called "Soul King;" you're basically their nemesis.
المقصود بالسول في لقب بروك هي موسيقى السول غير أن للسول معنى آخر وهو الأرواح وهو ما تعنيه بيغ مام هنا
But,
...ولكن
you were unable to defeat these guys.
لا يمكنك هزيمة هؤلاء الثلاثة
Napoleon, a Bicorne Hat
نابليون، قبعة قديمة الطراز
Zeus, a Storm Cloud
زيوس، غيمة رعدية
Prometheus, a Sun
بروميثيوس، شمس
I gave them my soul, so they're a part of me.
لقد وهبتهم روحي مباشرة
That means their souls are in a different class.
لذا روحهم مختلفة تمامًا
We finished our inspection, Mama!
انتهينا من التفتيش يا ماما
He isn't hiding anything in his clothes!
لا يوجد شيء في ملابسه
And he doesn't have anything in this tube!
ولا بهذه الحقيبة
Nor in his cane sword...
ولا في سيفه وغمده
And not within his cloak.
ولا في وشاحه
He has nothing!
ليس هناك شيء
He didn't steal anything!
لم يسرق شيئًا
That's good to hear, Soul King.
هذا جيّد إذًا يا ملك السول
I'm sorry that I suspected you. Pet, pet.
أعتذر عن اشتباهي بك
How frustrating. This is so humiliating.
يا لها من خيبة أمل، يا لها من إهانة
The Tamate Box is one thing,
موضوع صندوق تاماتي لا جدل فيه
but I wouldn't be able to let you get away with stealing my poneglyphs, either.
ولكن لا يمكنني السماح لك بسرقة نسخة من البونغليف أو أي غرض آخر أيضًا
It'd be foolish if I allowed another person to take them and reach Laugh Tale again.
سيكون من الغباء إذا سمحت لك بأخذه والسماح لشخص آخر بالوصول إلى جزيرة لافتيل مجددًا
I won't make the same mistake that I did with Roger!
لن أسمح بتدهور الأمور كما حصل مع روجر
He used that strange ability to hear the Voice of All Things and read the stone.
لقد قرأ الحجر بواسطة قدرته الغريبة التي تسمح له بسماع صوت كل شيء
But now I've got someone capable of using a similar ability.
ولكن لدينا شخص سيتمكن من الحصول على قدرة مشابهة لقدرته
The next to reach Laugh Tale... will be us!
نحن فقط من سيصل إلى جزيرة لافتيل تاليًا ولا أحد سوانا
Mama!
ماما
Oh, my dear Pudding! I was just talking about you.
بودينغ اللطيفة، كنا نتحدث عنك للتو يا عزيزتي
What's up? Has your third eye finally revealed its power?
ما الأمر؟ هل أيقظتِ القوى الحقيقية لعينك الثالثة؟
Come on, Mama! You ask me that every time you see me!
بحقك يا ماما، أنتِ تقولين هذا في كل مرة تريني فيها
I'm a half-blood, remember?
أنا هجينة
There's no guarantee that I'll ever be able to use that ability.
ليس هناك ما يضمن استيقاظ مثل هذه القوى بي
I'm sorry.
المعذرة
But you do have the blood of the three-eye people in your veins.
ولكن دماء آل العيون الثلاثة النادرة تجري في شرايينك حتمًا
If you don't awaken your latent ability as a three-eye,
إن لم تستيقظ تلك القوى كفرد يندرج من دماء آل العيون الثلاثة
you'll be nothing but a creepy girl.
فلستِ سوى فتاة قبيحة المنظر
P-Pudding-san...
بودينغ-سان؟
has three eyes?
العيون الثلاثة؟
No!
سيئ
The fact that we know each other...
...حقيقة أننا نعرف بعضنا البعض
That's that skeleton man.
الهيكل العظمي؟
I didn't expect to see him here. Well, at least they caught him.
لم أتوقع وجوده هنا، لقد قُبض عليه لذا لا مشكلة
Um, Mama? I don't feel comfortable talking to you in here. Can we go to your room?
من المُحرج التحدث إليكِ هنا يا ماما، لذا فلنذهب إلى غرفتك
Ah, of course! Anything for you.
حسنًا، لا مشكلة
That call is...
...هذا الصياح
He's about to evolve into his third form!
هل سيتطور إلى الهيئة الثالثة؟
He's turning into Count Niwatori!
هل سيتطور إلى نيواتوري هاكوشاكو؟
This is stupid.
سخافة
I'll finish him off now.
سأتخلص منه حالًا
Stop!
توقف
First was Baron Tamago; then Viscount Hiyoko; and now it's Count Niwatori! Note: Tamago (Egg) – Hiyoko (Chick) – Niwatori (Chicken)
من البارون تاماغو إلى هيوكو شيكاكو ومن ثم الآن إلى نيواتوري هاكوشاكو
The more he transforms, the more powerful he gets!
تزداد قوته كلما تطوّر
He ate the Egg-Egg Fruit!
إنه يتمتع بقدرة فاكهة البيض
Count Niwatori is a true knight! You should be terrified!
نيواتوري هاكوشاكو هو فارس حقيقي يجب أن ترتعد خوفًا منه
Once he transforms fully, he'll have power that you'll be no match for!
سيحظى بقوة لن تكون قادرًا على مجابهتها حالما ينتهي من تطوّره
Stop him from disrupting the transformation!
أوقفوه
I'm not going to just sit around and watch.
لن أنتظر
Stop!
توقف
Fine, I'll stop.
إذًا سأتوقف
This is it.
هذه هي النهاية
It's nice to have so many soldiers around.
من جيّد وجود العديد من الجنود
You bastard! What are you doing?!
ماذا تفعل أيها الوغد؟
Pull back!
تراجعوا
Run away!
اهربوا
A decoy couldn't ask for more.
ومن الجيّد أن تكون طعمًا
Don't do it!
توقف
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Oh, that was close! You could've been killed, Pedro!
كان ذلك وشيكًا، كدت تهلك يا بيدرو
You're so reckless!
يا لك من متهور
Pedro, you really startled me there.
لقد أفزعتني يا بيدرو
You startled me more.
أنا مفزوع أكثر منك
Hey, Pedro!
يا بيدرو
Imagine if you were in my position, and a mirror spoke to you.
فمن كان سيتخيّل أن تتم مناداته فجأة من داخل مرآة؟
But you managed to come up with a plan without a second thought!
ولكنك استنبطت خطة كهذه مباشرة كما هو متوقع منك يا بيدرو
In any case, we're inside of the mirrors?
على أيّ حال، أنحن بداخل المرايا؟
This is pretty outlandish.
يصعب تصديق هذا
No one can come in or get out of here without Brûlée. We'll be safe here!
لا يمكن لأحد الدخول أو الخروج من عالم المرايا دون بروليه، لذا نحن بأمان هنا
If we find Sanji, we can escape through here with him!
بوسعنا الهرب مع سانجي باستخدام هذا البُعد
Tell us what you've learned!
أخبرنا بما تعرفه
What?!
ماذا؟
Luffy and Nami got caught?!
لوفي ونامي قد قُبض عليهما؟
Yeah, that's what I heard.
أجل، هذا ما سمعته
I'm worried about Brook too.
أنا قلق على بروك أيضًا
Let's hope he managed to get a copy of that poneglyph.
آمل أنّه حصل على نسخة من البونغليف دون متاعب
They're all in danger! Let's hurry up!
جمعيهم في خطر، فلنسرع
Carrot! Did you finish drawing everyone's portrait?
كاروت، هل صور الجميع جاهزة؟
Yes I did, Chobro!
أجل، الصور جاهزة يا تشونيكي
You did?! Good job!
حقًّا؟ هذا مذهل
Then, let's show the portraits to the mirrors in order to get their locations.
إذًا فلنبحث عن الجميع بعرض صورهم على المرايا
Okay!
حسنًا
Mirror, mirror! Tell us where these people are!
أيتها المرايا، أخبرينا عن أماكن هؤلاء
They look nothing like them!
ليس هُنالك شبه على الإطلاق
That girl with the long hair just ran past me!
تلك الفتاة ذات الشعر الطويل قد مرّت من هنا قبل قليل
The mirror talked!
المرآة قد تكلمت
What? So, did Nami break out? Is she with Luffy?
ماذا؟ أهذا يعني أنّ نامي قد هربت؟ أهي مع لوفي؟
She was with Boss Jinbe!
إنّها برفقة الزعيم جينبي
J... Jinbe?
جـ-جينبي؟
W-W-What?!
ماذا؟
Sanji!
سانجي
Third Floor Midbaum
الدور الثالث، باوم
Answer me if you're here!
أجبني إن كنت تسمعني
Stop, Straw Hat!
توقف يا قبعة القش
Sanji!
سانجي
I've got something to tell you! Where are you?!
ثمة ما يجب أن أخبرك به، أين أنت؟
You gotta hear me out!
استمع لما سأخبرك به
Where did Straw Hat go?
أين ذهب قبعة القش؟
He's too fast! Which way did he go?
ما أسرعه، أي طريق سلك؟
Did he go in here?
أهو بالداخل؟
The door won't open!
إنّه موصد
Let's go that way!
فلنذهب من هذا الاتجاه
Yeah!
أجل
You're... Sanji's sister!
أنتِ أُخت سانجي
That's correct.
صحيح
What do you want? I'm in a hurry here!
لِمَ فعلتِ هذا؟ إني في عجلة من أمري
What? Really?! Where'd he go?!
ماذا؟ حقًّا؟ أين ذهب؟
Pudding lied to us!
كانت بودينغ تخدعنا
Pudding—who Sanji thinks he's marrying— told me that she's gonna kill him!
عروسة سانجي المدعوة بودينغ قالت أنّها ستقتله
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
هل أنتِ بخير؟ هل أُصبتِ؟
Thanks for asking. I'm fine.
شكرًا لك، أنا بخير
In any case, my brother already knows about Pudding.
كما أنّ أخي يعرف بشأن بودينغ
What?! Has he known the whole time?!
ماذا؟ أكان يعرف طيلة الوقت؟
He just found out about her.
اكتشفَ ذلك قبل فترة وجيزة
I tried to convince him to escape from this island,
لقد أقنعته بالهرب من هذه الجزيرة
but he was worried about the hostages in the East Blue...
ولكنَّ الرهائن في الأزرق الشرقي والضرر الذي قد يلحق بكم يشغلان تفكيره
Hostages? Do you mean the people at the Baratie?
أتقصدين باراتي بالرهائن؟
I know them too. If they're really in any danger, I'll go back to the East Blue and fight to protect them!
تربطني بهم علاقة جيّدة، إن كانوا حقًّا بخطر سأتجه نحو الأزرق الشرقي وأحارب لأجلهم
Do you want to eat something?
أتريد طعامًا؟
N-No, I'll be fine!
لا أريد
I'll be here waiting!
سأظلّ منتظرًا هنا
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...إن لم تعد، فسأظلّ هنا
starving to death!
حتّى أموت جوعًا
You're the cook of my ship!
أنت طاهي سفينتي
I won't eat anything other than what you cook!
لن أتناول شيئًا سوى ما تطهوه
But... this is good.
...ولكن هذا مطمئن أنّ سانجي
Sanji knows about Pudding.
أنّ سانجي عرف بشأن حقيقة بودينغ
As long as he's not being tricked, I'm happy.
إن لم يتم خداعه، فهذا جيّد بالنسبة لي
I've done everything else I can!
وأيضًا، لقد فعلت ما بوسعي
Okay, thank you, Sanji's sister!
حسنًا، شكرًا لكِ يا أُخت سانجي
What? Why are you going that way?!
لـ-لِمَ تسلك هذا الاتجاه؟
This isn't where I promised to meet him!
لقد وعدته بانتظاره، لكن ليس هنا
Sanji!
سانجي
...want us to chop his head off.
سنقطع رأس هذا الرجل
You are a sacrifice, Sanji.
أنت قربانٌ يا سانجي
As long as you don't try to run away, everything will work out just fine, Sanji.
ما دمت لن تهرب، فكل شيء سيسير على ما يرام يا سانجي
At the wedding tomorrow...
...أنتم يا عائلة فينسموك
the entire Vinsmoke family...
...غدًا في حفلة الزفاف
will be executed!
سيُقضى عليكم جميعًا
Begone from my sight, you miserable, lowlife pirate!
عُد أدراجك أيها القرصان الوضيع البائس
It's too late for me to turn back, Luffy.
فات الأوان على التراجع يا لوفي
Oh! Something hit my house!
شيءٌ ما أصاب المنزل
My house!
منزلي
What's going on? It's so late.
ما الذي يجري في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
Is that a person?
شخص؟
H-Hey! Are you okay?
مهلًا، هل أنت بخير؟
We found you.
ها هو الرجل المنشود
I gotta get there as soon as possible.
يجب أن أصل هناك بأسرع وقت
I'll be here waiting!
سأظلّ منتظرًا هنا
I've gotta be waiting...
يجب أن أكون هناك وأنتظره
at that spot!
في نقطة الملتقى
Block off the exits!
احجبوا طريقهما
Oh, no! We're about to be surrounded.
سيئ، أظن أنّهم سيحاصروننا
What? Isn't there a way out?
ماذا؟ ألا يوجد طريق للخروج؟
Can you handle the rear, Nami?
أيمكنكِ تولي أمر من في الخلف يا نامي؟
You can count on me! I'm getting tired of this.
اعتمد علي، فقد ضقت ذرعًا من هذا الوضع
There they are!
وجدتهما
Stop!
توقفا
Nami!
نامي
You guys are annoying!
أنتم مزعجون
Thundercloud Rod!
عاصفة سحابة رود
What?! Chopper!
ماذا؟ تشوبر؟
Chopper! Why are you here?!
تشوبر، لِمَ أنت هنا؟
Oh! Chobro!
تشونيكي؟
Carrot!
كاروت؟
Nami! We're here to save you!
نامي، لقد أتينا لإنقاذك
I see! I'm so sorry!
فهمت، أعتذر
Oh, no! There are more enemies up ahead.
هذا سيئ، المزيد من الأعداء قادمون من الأمام
Nami! Get in the mirror now!
نامي، ادخلي المرآة حالًا
What?
ماذا؟
Oh, ow, ow!
مؤلم، مؤلم
What's the matter, Prometheus?
ما الخطب يا بروميثيوس؟
Queen's Chamber Whole Cake Chateau
قصر الكعكة الكاملة غرفة الملكة
The wound I got from Soul King is deeper than I thought,
تلك الندبة التي ألحقها بي ملك السول كانت أعمق مما توقعت
and now it's starting to hurt again!
لقد انفتحت مرة أخرى
I mean, we should give him some credit.
ولكن يجب أن نثني عليه
Because no one's ever been able to hurt you guys before.
فلم يسبق لأحد أن ألحق بكم الأذى من قبل
Mama, are you really going to keep holding onto that skeleton?
ماما، هل ستبقين هذا الهيكل العظمي هنا للأبد؟
What? "That skeleton"? Pudding-san, how could you refer to me like that?
ماذا؟ «هذا الهيكل العظمي»؟ كيف لكِ أن تناديني بهذا الوصف يا بودينغ-سان؟
Yeah, of course!
أجل، بالطبع
Too close!
قريبة جدًّا
There's no other creature like this! It's a work of soul art!
لا يوجد لدي مخلوق مثله، إنّه إبداع من فن الروح
I'd rather carry him around for a while instead of putting him in a book.
سأحمله معي بدلًا من رميه بأحد الكتب
No...
مستحيل
Good job on tricking the Straw Hats.
لقد أبليتِ حسنًا مع طاقم قبعة القش
I never expected them to get through the Seducing Woods.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن يقدروا على عبور غابة الإغواء
But now they're trapped in a book in the Prisoner Library.
ولكننا تمكنا من حبسهم داخل أحد الكتب الموجودة في مكتبة السجناء
Yeah, I went to see them, too. It serves them right.
أجل، ذهبت لرؤيتهم أيضًا، لقد نالوا ما يستحقون
"It serves them right"?
نالوا ما يستحقون؟ ماذا؟
Are you gonna kill them?
هل ستقتليهم؟
Yeah, after the wedding ceremony.
أجل، بعد حفلة الزفاف
I sent barmaids over to Germa.
أرسلت فتيات الحانة إلى جميع أفراد جيرما
They're probably in a drunken stupor right now and won't be expecting anything!
أظن أنّ جميعهم سكارى الآن ولا يدركون ما ينتظرهم
Good... But Reiju was investigating me.
فهمت، ولكن ريجو كانت تبحث بشأني
She's a pretty sharp person. It's a good thing I took care of her.
إنّها فتاة فطنة، ولكنني تكفلت بأمرها
What? You didn't kill her, right?!
ماذا؟ لم تقتليها، صحيح؟
Come on, Mama! Don't you trust me?! I just shot her leg!
مهلًا، ألا تثقين بي يا ماما؟ لقد أصبت ساقها بعيار ناري وحسب
I shot her once, and then erased her memories.
أصبتها ومسحت ذكرياتها
I can't believe this.
لا أصدق ما أسمعه
Pudding-san ? Aren't you a sweet girl?
بودينغ-سان، كنتُ أظن أنّكِ فتاة طيّبة
You need to be careful. You're my precious bride.
احذري، أنتِ عروستنا العزيزة
It'd be a major problem if she tried to get revenge.
إذا حاولت الانتقام منكِ، فستعم الفوضى المكان
Thank you for your concern, Mama. But...
...شكرًا على قلقك يا ماما، ولكنني
thanks to her, I got to test out this gun.
تمكنت من تجربة مسدسي بفضلها
With this gun, even Germa's modified bodies won't stand a chance.
يمكنني اختراق أجساد جيرما البشرية المعدلة بواسطة رصاص هذا المسدس
That's great, very great.
فهمت، فهمت
You're such a smart girl.
يا لكِ من فتاة ذكية
When you open fire tomorrow, that'll be the signal for our plan to begin.
سيكون رصاص مسدسك غدًا بمثابة شرارة البداية
I can't wait.
أتطلع ليوم الغد
Everyone will be watching when it's time for the wedding kiss.
سيكون الجميع في حالة ترقّب لقُبلة الزفاف
That dopey-faced Sanji will lift your veil and try to kiss you.
سانجي ذا الوجه القبيح سيحاول رفع حجاب وجهك وتقبيلك
That's when...
...تلك اللحظة بالضبط
he'll see your third eye for the first time!
سيرى عينك الثالثة لأول مرة
In that moment, he'll see his beautiful bride's creepy face,
في اللحظة التي يرى فيها الوجه الحقيقي والمخيف لعروسته الجميلة
and he'll be distracted for a moment!
سيتراجع للوراء قليلًا
That'll be your cue, okay? You'll have to finish him off with one shot.
في تلك اللحظة أشهري سلاحك وأرديه قتيلًا بطلقة واحدة
Aim right between his eyes! Right here.
وقومي بتوجيه مسدسك على منتصف حاجبيه، هنا بالضبط
Pudding-san is going to kill Sanji-san ?!
بودينغ-سان ستقتل سانجي-سان؟
Everyone will be in shock, unable to move.
كل شخص في القاعة سيُصاب بالذهول وسيتجمد مكانه
The people of Germa will realize they're in danger and try to run,
الجيرما سيُصيبهم الاضطراب، وفي حين محاولتهم في الابتعاد والهرب
but it'll already be too late at that point!
يكون الأوان قد فات
As the unarmed Vinsmokes turn around to run, they'll notice a wall of guns pointing at them!
أعداد كبيرة من الأسلحة ستكون موجهة نحو عائلة الفينسموك الغير مسلّحين
They won't even have time to show fear before their blood spills.
دماء الجريما ستُراق قبل أن يُدرك الخوف قلوبهم حتّى
Gunshots will be going off like fireworks!
أصوات طلقات النار لن تتوقف كالألعاب النارية
A rain of bullets will continue to pierce their bodies, even long after they die!
وابل من الرصاص سيستمر بثقب أجسادهم حتّى بعد مماتهم
There'll be a giant pool of blood spreading on the ground!
دماءٌ تتناثر على الأرضية
The six Vinsmokes will be nothing but mutiliated corpses!
جثث هامدة لعائلة الفينسموك الستة
The gunshots will be shots of joy!
العيارات النارية ستُصبح رصاصات فرح وبهجة
And that's when the real party begins!
وحينها ستبدأ الحفلة الحقيقية
We'll celebrate with the cake. We'll toast with tea!
سنحتفل بالكعكة، ونحتسي الشاي
Once they lose their useless leader,
حينما يخسرون حياة قائدهم عديم الجدوى
all of Germa will belong to me!
ستغدو قوة جريما العلمية ملكي
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Are you okay, Chobro?
هل أنت بخير يا تشونيكي؟
I can't believe it! We're inside the mirror?!
لا أصدق هذا، هل نحن بداخل المرآة حقًّا؟
Jinbe! Why are you with these rats?!
جينبي، لِمَ أنت برفقة هؤلاء الجرذان؟
Brûlée.
بروليه
This is obviously treason.
هذه خيانة صريحة
I heard you tried to leave our crew, but when faced with the roulette, you cowered in fear!
سمعتُ أنّك أردت مغادرة طاقمنا ولكنك تراجعت بسبب الروليت
I wanted to repay Mama for protecting Fishman Island after Whitebeard's death.
أنا مدين بالفعل لماما لحمايتها جزيرة البرمائيين بعد موت اللحية البيضاء
Since I wanted to leave, I wanted to do so honorably for her sake.
أردت أن أرد الدين لها بما أني كنت عازمًا على الرحيل
But I could only sense death and malice from that roulette.
ولكنني لم ألتمس من ذلك الروليت سوى نوايا القتل والشر
A roulette?
روليت؟
You made the correct choice not to spin it, Jinbe, Knight of the Sea.
أحسنت بعدم فعلها يا فارس البحر جينبي
Five years ago, my partner turned that roulette wheel and asked Big Mom for mercy,
قبل خمسة سنوات، قام شريكي بتدوير عجلة الروليت ملتمسًا رحمة بيغ مام
but he lost his life instead.
وفقد حياته جرّاء ذلك
Those that spin that thing are guaranteed to die. It was made that way.
لقد صُنِعَت لسلب حياة من يقوم بتدويرها
So it's rigged?!
إذًا هي مزيفة؟
Of course it is, you fools! Mama would never let anyone leave alive!
بالطبع هي كذلك أيها الحمقى لن تدع ماما أحد يغادر مملكتها على قيد الحياة
Whether it's a minor intruder
سواءً كان الشخص دخيل عادي
or an affiliated pirate who was once loyal!
أو قرصان تابع تحت اسمها كان يكن لها الولاء ذات يوم
She welcomes all who come to this land
إنّها ترحّب بجميع القادمين
and kills those who leave!
وتقتل من يودّ المغادرة
That's Mama's–
تلك هي طبيعة ماما
We don't have time for this!
الوقت يداهمنا
Let's keep moving! We need to find Brook, Luffy, and Sanji!
فلنذهب، يجب أن نلتقي ببروك ولوفي وسانجي
I'm not moving again! There's too many of you!
لن أغادر، الحمولة زائدة
Sanji's Room
غرفة سانجي
That's right. Prince Sanji, the groom, is fast asleep in his room.
أجل، العريس سانجي-ساما نائم في غرفته بالطبع
Don't let him out or let anyone in until morning. Keep a close eye on that door.
راقب غرفته جيّدًا ولا تسمح بخروجه أو بدخول أي أحد لغرفته حتّى الصباح
Yes, ma'am!
حاضر
Oh, no! I fell asleep-nasu ! In Prince Sanji's bed!
سحقًا، لقد غططت بالنوم في سرير سانجي-ساما
Is he not back yet-nasu ?
ألم يعد سانجي-ساما بعد-ناسو؟
I guess he won't come back any time soon-nasu.
لا أظنه سيعود مبكرًا-ناسو
Well, I might as well sleep a little more-nasu.
إذًا سأنام قليلًا-ناسو
In other words,
بعبارة أخرى، بيكومز كان برفقتهم حتّى وصلوا إلى بلدة الشوكولاتة
Meeting Room
غرفة الاجتماعات
They're trying to get Sanji back.
إذًا فهدفهم هو استعادة سانجي كما توقعنا فعلًا
There were six of them when Pudding lured them to the main island.
جلبت بودينغ ستة أشخاص لهذه الجزيرة
Mama has Soul King now.
أصبح ملك السول دمية بيد ماما
Don't touch this!
لا تلمسوها
And Pedro was in the courtyard on the third floor when he blew himself up, right?
وبيدرو فجّر نفسه في فناء الطابق الثالث، صحيح؟
Indeed-cock-a-doo.
بالفعل-كوكي
That's two taken care of.
سقط اثنان
And of the four who entered the Seducing Woods... the rabbit and raccoon dog...
وبالنسبة للأربعة الذين دخلوا غابة الإغواء، فالأرنبة والراكون
were caught by Big Sis Brûlée. She informed us of this earlier today.
قد قُبض عليهما من قبل أختنا بروليه وأبلغت عن ذلك ظهر اليوم
That means we've taken care of four of the six. That leaves...
مما يعني أنّه سقط أربعة ...من أصل ستة، والمعضلة حاليًّا
the two who defeated Big Brother Cracker and escaped from the Seducing Woods.
تكمن في هذين الاثنان اللذان هزما أخانا كراكر وهربا من غابة الإغواء
They were definitely imprisoned in the underground Prisoner Library.
أنا متأكد بأننا قمنا بحبسهما داخل مكتبة السجن في القبو
So why are we getting reports that they escaped?
ولكن، لِمَ توجد إشاعات تُفيد بهربهما؟
Only one of us was there in the Prisoner Library.
واحد منا كان في مكتبة السجن
What happened, Big Brother Opera? What's this about Jinbe showing up?
ما الذي حدث يا أخي أوبرا؟ ثمة أقاويل تتداول حول ظهور جينبي من العدم
It's a lie! Don't make me repeat myself!
هذا باطل، لا تجعلني أكرر كلامي
In fact, where is he now?
أين هو الآن؟
Nobody has reported a thing! Nobody came down to the basement!
لا توجد أي معلومات عنه إطلاقًا، ولم يدخل أحد القبو
As Mama ordered, I was trying to get Lola's whereabouts out of them!
لقد كنتُ أعذبهما لمعرفة مكان لولا كما طلبت مني ماما
They didn't know anything, so I burned them alive!
لم يكن في جعبتهما أي معلومات عن مكانها، لذا قتلتهما حرقًا
I know I went a little overboard.
أعترف بأني قد بالغت قليلًا في ذلك
D-Don't you trust your older brother, Mont d'Or?!
أ-أيعقل أنّك لا تثق بأخيك يا مونت دور؟
Of course I do.
أثق بك بالطبع
There's no way I can admit that I let them get away! Never ever!
لا يمكنني إخبارهم بأني فشلت في حراستهما أبدًا
Mama will take away my lifespan if she finds out!
ستسلبني ماما حياتي كلها
What about Sanji and the Vinsmokes?
ما وضع سانجي وعائلة الفينسموك؟
They're in their rooms.
جميعهم في غرفهم
Okay, then everything is fine!
عظيم، كل شيء ما يُرام
All the intruders have been caught!
لقد قُبض على كل الدخلاء
Right now, in the great kitchen, they're preparing the feast for tomorrow!
في الوقت الراهن كل من في المطبخ العملاق يستعدون ليوم غد
Let's make tomorrow the greatest wedding ever for our precious little sister, Pudding!
فلنجعل زفاف أختنا العزيزة بودينغ يوم غدٍ أعظم حفل زفاف على الإطلاق
Yeah!
أجل
Cover more ground and continue to patrol through the night.
وسّعوا نطاق حراستكم ودورياتكم حتّى الصباح
Yes, sir!
حاضر
I can't trust Opera on this one.
أنا لا أثق بأوبرا
Medical Room Third Floor
الدور الثالث الغرفة الطبية
Sweet City
مدينة الحلوى
In the Chateau
في القصر
My goodness... Did I make this for Pudding-chan ?
بحق، هل أعددت كل هذا من أجل بودينغ-تشان؟
What was I thinking?
بِمَ كنتُ أفكر؟
I made their favorite foods.
إنّها وجباتهم المفضلة
Forget them! Forget them!
انسَ أمرهم، انسَ أمرهم
I don't need to worry about Luffy and the others. They can escape on their own.
ليس عليّ القلق على لوفي والرفاق بإمكانهم الهرب بمفردهم
The evil army of Vinsmokes will die, and so will I.
كل أفراد جيش فينسموك الأشرار سيهلكون، وأنا معهم أيضًا
It'll all go according to Big Mom's plan.
كما خططت بيغ مام
Mont d'Or said you were sleeping in your room.
لقد قال مونت دور أنّك نائم في غرفتك
If you don't come back, I'll be here...
...إن لم تعد، فسأظلّ هنا
starving to death!
حتّى أموت جوعًا
Don't touch that!
أبعد يدك
doesn't belong to you!
ليس لك
I heard a loud noise down the hall!
سمعتُ ضوضاء تصدر من ذلك الاتجاه
You son of a...
...أيها الوغد
Hey, stop, you bastard!
مهلًا أيها الوغد
What the hell am I doing?
ما الذي أفعله؟